▍2026 多伦多 WTA1000 第二轮
萨巴伦卡 6-3 6-3 内岛萌夏 · 赛后场上采访
Well, Aryna,
阿丽娜
great to have you back here in Toronto
很高兴你回到多伦多
and you had to be at your best tonight,
今晚你必须拿出最好的状态
a tough opening round match for you,
首场就是一场硬仗
but you're through, how do you assess
但你过关了 你怎么评价
your performance after tonight?
今晚自己的表现？
Yeah, not an easy match, after a little break,
嗯 不轻松 休息了一阵之后
super happy to be through and happy
能过关我非常高兴 也很高兴
to be back in Toronto
回到多伦多
and see you all tonight, it was amazing,
今晚见到你们 太棒了
thank you, thank you so much.
谢谢 真的谢谢
We love having you back,
我们也很高兴你回来
I wanted to ask you about your break,
想问问你的假期
you went to Vienna with Ash,
你带着阿什去了维也纳
your Cavalier King Charles Spaniel,
你那只查理王小猎犬
with your fiancé Georgios,
还有未婚夫乔治奥斯
to have a little break from tennis,
离开网球休息一阵
are you feeling refreshed,
现在觉得恢复了吗
are you feeling ready
准备好迎接
for the hard court season?
硬地赛季了吗？
I went to Vienna before Wimbledon,
温网之前我去了维也纳
then I went to Mykonos after Wimbledon,
温网之后又去了米克诺斯
so there was much needed,
那是真的需要
there was so much needed, I feel refreshed,
太需要了 我觉得恢复了
recharged and ready to go.
充满电 准备好了
Great stuff, listen, your hard court record
太好了 你今年的硬地战绩
has been phenomenal this year,
好得惊人
24 victories out of 25, do you feel you're
二十五场赢了二十四场
your best here on the hard court,
硬地上的你 是最好的自己吗
are you feeling really comfortable playing
回到硬地打球
back on the hard court?
你觉得真的舒服吗？
I feel definitely happy to be back
我确实很高兴 这个赛季
on hard court this season.
能回到硬地